a:8:{s:8:"encoding";s:5:"UTF-8";s:5:"title";s:27:"Education and Literacy NEWS";s:4:"link";s:26:"http://www.news.gov.bc.ca/";s:11:"description";s:52:"The latest headlines by theme Education and Literacy";s:8:"language";s:5:"en-us";s:9:"copyright";s:47:"Copyright © 2010, Province of British Columbia";s:5:"items";a:10:{i:0;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:45:"NEW CLASSROOM SPACE BENEFITS STUDENTS AT COTR";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010RESD0002-001347.htm";s:11:"description";s:198:"CRANBROOK – Students at the College of the Rockies will enjoy a new and improved place to study and learn with the completion of a major $12.74-million expansion and renovation of Kootenay Centre.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Fri, 29 Oct 2010 22:34:46 GMT";}i:1;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:48:"EIGHT NEW CLASSROOMS FOR SHANNON LAKE ELEMENTARY";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010EDUC0120-001351.htm";s:11:"description";s:256:"KELOWNA – The Central Okanagan school district is breaking ground on a $2.6-million addition at Shannon Lake Elementary school that will create 185 student spaces for full-day kindergarten and enrolment growth, Westside-Kelowna MLA Ben Stewart announced.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Fri, 29 Oct 2010 18:09:17 GMT";}i:2;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:52:"CAMOSUN CELEBRATES DYNAMIC $4-MILLION REVITALIZATION";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010RESD0001-001345.htm";s:11:"description";s:301:"VICTORIA – Camosun College is celebrating completion of three of its Knowledge Infrastructure Program projects, including an expanded fitness centre and new learning commons at the Lansdowne campus, and a new learning commons at the Interurban campus, giving students even more dynamic environments.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Fri, 29 Oct 2010 16:46:59 GMT";}i:3;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:52:"NIC CELEBRATES OPENING OF ABORIGINAL GATHERING PLACE";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010RESD0003-001348.htm";s:11:"description";s:184:"PORT ALBERNI – Aboriginal students at North Island College’s Port Alberni campus have a new gathering place for traditional ceremonies and celebrations, supporting their community.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Fri, 29 Oct 2010 14:59:42 GMT";}i:4;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:51:"12 NEW CLASSROOMS, 270 NEW STUDENT SPACES IN SURREY";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010EDUC0119-001344.htm";s:11:"description";s:196:"SURREY – Three schools will start work in December on four-classroom additions totalling $5.2 million that will help provide space for full-day kindergarten and help address enrolment increases.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:18:20 GMT";}i:5;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:48:"UVIC RATIFIES AGREEMENT WITH FACULTY ASSOCIATION";s:4:"link";s:73:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010FIN0058-001306.htm";s:11:"description";s:208:"VICTORIA – A two-year agreement under the Province’s 2010 mandate has been ratified between the University of Victoria and members of the UVic Faculty Association, announced Finance Minister Colin Hansen.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Thu, 21 Oct 2010 18:01:10 GMT";}i:6;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:53:"FOUR CLASSROOMS, 90 NEW STUDENT SPACES FOR HAZELGROVE";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010EDUC0117-001301.htm";s:11:"description";s:236:"SURREY – Construction is set to begin in November on a $1.8-million four-classroom addition at Hazelgrove Elementary school to assist with full-day kindergarten and future enrolment needs, Surrey-Cloverdale MLA Kevin Falcon announced.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Thu, 21 Oct 2010 15:46:09 GMT";}i:7;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:48:"IMPROVED CRIMINAL RECORD CHECKS PROTECT CHILDREN";s:4:"link";s:73:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010CFD0024-001296.htm";s:11:"description";s:270:"VICTORIA – The Ministry of Children and Family Development has moved to further improve and enhance the criminal record check process for people who care for children and youth in the care of the ministry, announced Children and Family Development Minister Mary Polak.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Thu, 21 Oct 2010 14:48:34 GMT";}i:8;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:53:"EDUCATION, INNOVATION FOCUS OF TRAVEL TO ASIA, ISRAEL";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010ALMD0057-001287.htm";s:11:"description";s:330:"VANCOUVER – Minister of Advanced Education and Labour Market Development Moira Stilwell will be travelling to China and Vietnam to continue to develop and promote relationships with British Columbia’s educational institutions, and will then travel to Israel to meet with government and industry leaders in technology transfer.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Tue, 19 Oct 2010 17:44:04 GMT";}i:9;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:57:"$25,000 SCHOLARSHIP TO SUPPORT B.C.’S FUTURE SCIENTISTS";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010ALMD0056-001272.htm";s:11:"description";s:270:"BURNABY – One aspiring scientist will win a $25,000 education scholarship to pursue the career of their dreams as the grand prize in the Year of Science contest launched today at BCIT, announced Advanced Education and Labour Market Development Minister Moira Stilwell.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Mon, 18 Oct 2010 22:53:47 GMT";}}s:11:"items_count";i:10;}