a:8:{s:8:"encoding";s:5:"UTF-8";s:5:"title";s:26:"Ministry of Education NEWS";s:4:"link";s:26:"http://www.news.gov.bc.ca/";s:11:"description";s:46:"The latest headlines for Ministry of Education";s:8:"language";s:5:"en-us";s:9:"copyright";s:47:"Copyright © 2010, Province of British Columbia";s:5:"items";a:10:{i:0;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:48:"EIGHT NEW CLASSROOMS FOR SHANNON LAKE ELEMENTARY";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010EDUC0120-001351.htm";s:11:"description";s:256:"KELOWNA – The Central Okanagan school district is breaking ground on a $2.6-million addition at Shannon Lake Elementary school that will create 185 student spaces for full-day kindergarten and enrolment growth, Westside-Kelowna MLA Ben Stewart announced.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Fri, 29 Oct 2010 18:09:17 GMT";}i:1;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:51:"12 NEW CLASSROOMS, 270 NEW STUDENT SPACES IN SURREY";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010EDUC0119-001344.htm";s:11:"description";s:196:"SURREY – Three schools will start work in December on four-classroom additions totalling $5.2 million that will help provide space for full-day kindergarten and help address enrolment increases.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Thu, 28 Oct 2010 19:18:20 GMT";}i:2;a:3:{s:5:"title";s:35:"DROP EVERYTHING AND READ ON OCT. 25";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010EDUC0118-001315.htm";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Fri, 22 Oct 2010 14:54:42 GMT";}i:3;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:53:"FOUR CLASSROOMS, 90 NEW STUDENT SPACES FOR HAZELGROVE";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010EDUC0117-001301.htm";s:11:"description";s:236:"SURREY – Construction is set to begin in November on a $1.8-million four-classroom addition at Hazelgrove Elementary school to assist with full-day kindergarten and future enrolment needs, Surrey-Cloverdale MLA Kevin Falcon announced.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Thu, 21 Oct 2010 15:46:09 GMT";}i:4;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:54:"BIGGER, BETTER GARIBALDI SECONDARY OFFICIALLY RE-OPENS";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010EDUC0116-001246.htm";s:11:"description";s:204:"MAPLE RIDGE – Maple Ridge-Mission MLA Marc Dalton was joined by students, parents, teachers and community officials to celebrate the official re-opening of the expanded and upgraded Garibaldi Secondary.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Wed, 13 Oct 2010 23:56:59 GMT";}i:5;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:54:"B.C. COMPANY TO BUILD FULL DAY K MODULARS, CREATE JOBS";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010EDUC0115-001222.htm";s:11:"description";s:336:"VICTORIA – Shelter Industries of Aldergrove signed a $28.5-million contract with the Ministry of Education to design, build, deliver and install 133 modular classrooms for school districts across B.C. as the Province implements full-day kindergarten for all children in September 2011, announced Education Minister Margaret MacDiarmid";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Thu, 07 Oct 2010 18:09:21 GMT";}i:6;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:24:"WORLD TEACHERS' DAY 2010";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010EDUC0114-001200.htm";s:11:"description";s:108:"VICTORIA - Tuesday, Oct. 5 is World Teachers’ Day and I want to express my gratitude to B.C.’s teachers.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Mon, 04 Oct 2010 15:55:43 GMT";}i:7;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:51:"GROWING TAYLOR PARK ELEMENTARY BY 11 NEW CLASSROOMS";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010EDUC0113-001175.htm";s:11:"description";s:240:"BURNABY – One hundred full-day kindergarten students will be able to call Burnaby's Taylor Park Elementary home now that a $4.4-million addition is on the way Burnaby North MLA Richard T. Lee and Burnaby-Lougheed MLA Harry Bloy announced.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Fri, 01 Oct 2010 19:01:19 GMT";}i:8;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:53:"SURREY CELEBRATES OPENING OF WOODWARD HILL ELEMENTARY";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010EDUC0111-001165.htm";s:11:"description";s:244:"SURREY – Students, parents, teachers and community officials gathered at Woodward Hill Elementary to celebrate the official opening of the first school in Surrey designed to LEED Gold standard, Surrey-Panorama MLA Stephanie Cadieux announced.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Thu, 30 Sep 2010 20:10:38 GMT";}i:9;a:4:{s:5:"title";s:46:"BUILDING B.C. COMMUNITIES ONE SCHOOL AT A TIME";s:4:"link";s:74:"http://www2.news.gov.bc.ca/news_releases_2009-2013/2010EDUC0112-001170.htm";s:11:"description";s:220:"VICTORIA – School districts across B.C. will be partnering with local governments to make use of $2.85 million in School Community Connections grants from the province and create dynamic community space within schools.";s:7:"pubDate";s:29:"Thu, 30 Sep 2010 14:34:15 GMT";}}s:11:"items_count";i:10;}